

ALESSANDRA RINALDO

Junior Front-end Developer

CONTACTS

+39 370 10 63 379

rinaldoalessandra@gmail.com

www.alessandrarinaldo.com

ABOUT ME

I am an enthusiastic, sunny and creative person, goal oriented, hard worker, team player. I am also able to meet deadlines under pressure and work in a busy and multicultural environment.

Each of my previous experiences gave me the hard and soft skills necessary to learn fast and apply the best method to do the job assigned.

LANGUAGES

Italian - Native English - Advanced

SKILLS

HTML, CSS, ,Java, Javascript, Bootstraps, React, APIs, VS Code, IntelliJ Idea, CodeBlocks

EDUCATION

Istituto Tecnico Commerciale "Cesare Beccaria", Carbonia Italy.
July 2018

High School Degree (Diploma di Stato)

SheCodes Max, April 2024

Front-end Developer

WORK EXPERIENCES

Sales Development Representative, May 2023 - August 2023

Contact and qualify potential customers, track progress towards meeting sales goals, collaborate with the sales team to develop strategies for reaching sales targets, use customer relationship management (CRM) software to manage leads and sales activities

Human Resources Payroll Administrator, April 2019 - May 2023

Determining organisation's tax obligations by calculating national and council taxes as well as contributions, identifing, investigating and resolving discrepancies in timesheet and payroll records, completing payroll reports for record-keeping purposes

Headwaiter, September 2018 - January 2019

Processing payments, scheduling shifts, coaching employees, making sure that the customer service is at all times performed in a professional way